hawkersco.com 2014-12-20

# Hawkers | Privacy

Play Hawkers S.L. (“Hawkers”) is totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers. The Hawkers team members are customers themselves of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you - e.g. arranging for a product to be sent to you, carrying out credit and other security checks and for the purposes of customer research and profiling or where we have your express permission to do so.

**Your Consent**

We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party without your permission, but we cannot be responsible or held liable for the actions of third party sites from which you may have linked or been directed to the Hawkers website.

**Communication and Marketing**

If you have made a purchase from our store we may occasionally update you on our latest products, news and special offers via e-mail, post and telephone. You will also be given the opportunity to receive such communications from us and selected third parties when you buy Hawkers product.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small information file that is sent to your computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website and it will recognise your device on future visits. These types of files do a number of different jobs such as remembering your preferences and chosen items, assisting you to improve your site experience as well as trying to ensure that the adverts or offers you see online are more relevant to you. These “cookies” can be divided into 4 types each of which is outlined below.

**Site Statistics**

We may disclose aggregate, anonymised statistics about the number of visitors to this Website or number of purchases made as required by our investors. We use an independent measurement and research company to gather data regarding the visitors to this Website on our behalf using cookies and code which is embedded in the site. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings and other general information. Hawkers uses and stores this type of information, as with that obtained from other cookies used on the site, to help it improve the services to its users.

**Protecting your security**

We may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti-fraud checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. This is done only to confirm your identity - a credit check is not performed and your credit rating is unaffected.

**Transfers of your Information**

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for Hawkers or one of our suppliers. Such processing may, for example, be required in order to fulfil your order, process your payment details or provide support services.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal data, but cannot guarantee the security of data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**Disclosures of your information**

We may disclose your personal information to any of our group of companies. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:

In the event that Hawkers sells or buys any business or assets: · if Hawkers or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data which we hold about our customers may be one of the transferred assets. · if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Hawkers, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Third party sites**

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Contacting us**

You can contact us at contact@hawkersco.com
